{
    "id": "0ce425c6cf87404093f3c0823097d3e7",
    "title": "Simple Past Or Past Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ............................. I didn't hear the door bell.",
            "description": "We use the past continuous to talk about an action or situation that was going on at a particular point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "slept",
                "was sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "795d12dcf809429aa6efdea39af11d0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ......................... her many times but she didn't answer.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "phoned",
                "was phoning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc6b6e4a26c8400c8763a42eab3bd093"
        },
        {
            "question": "'What ........................... then?' 'I was watching TV.'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did you do",
                "were you doing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "474b3cb9acac4b58bd9775122688a98b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ......................... money from the rich and gave it to the poor.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about all types of finished actions in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "stole",
                "was stealing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e969f2ab2ba84ab487eaed9501888a30"
        },
        {
            "question": "'Did you meet James yesterday?' 'Yes, I .................... him.'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "was meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1b576b5bab24185a00d8f2cb341352b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train ...................... at",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about finished actions in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "was arriving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "994f51d02a3243d390c25afe53650b2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ............................. when their mother .................... home.",
            "description": "When we talk about two past events, the past continuous is used to refer to the longer background action. ",
            "answers": [
                "slept, got",
                "were sleeping, was getting",
                "were sleeping, got"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d44c0e241ae34d7f8dcd3331d774b61e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cooked dinner while Mike ............................ the house.",
            "description": "The past simple can be used to talk about two actions that happened at the same time. ",
            "answers": [
                "was tidying",
                "tidied"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df41cffb1670450ba5cc697ab7ec1c46"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... dinner when the lights went out.",
            "description": "The past continuous can be used to talk about a longer background action that was going on when another action took place. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "was having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "875aa0c6a6ac4fff8b7e736d052f08be"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ......................... me quite sometime to learn French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "was taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4443e12e9d35429fb9ac377927876588"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I .............................. down the street, I saw a strange sight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "walked",
                "was walking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57542cf326bd4c03908ecb499adb5376"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................... a car last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "was buying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f80c5db4e2614637b3a8bb11f1bfcd36"
        }
    ]
}